Website: www.dannoot.tech

Email: khoa_dang_nguyen@hotmail.com

Danny Nguyen

(ie. Dang Khoa Nguyen)

Adelaide, South Australia +61 434 588 098

SUMMARY

I am a self-motivated and enthusiastic university student with 4 years of work experience in a range of different roles. Currently seeking an internship opportunity within the engineering industry that will allow me to learn and apply my academic learnings and complement theory with practice.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Kong Bros Catering

Team Waiter

March 2019 - February 2020

- A position that utilized strong team-work skills, time-management, the ability to work under pressure, and attention to
 detail. This would aid any future positions the ability to think effectively and quickly under pressure is essential for a role
 in the engineering industry.
- Set up, decorate and prepare serving and dining area according to specific directions and layout plan established by the catering manager.

Tiger's Chang Moo Kwan Taekwondo Academy

Instructor

February 2017 – November 2017

- Part-time role that involved instructing afternoon Taekwondo classes for kids and teenagers. Duties ranged from coordinating drills, teaching technique, and maintenance of the gym.
- A challenging experience that required patience, leadership skills, and communications to ensure everybody was learning, having fun, and keeping safe. The skills developed in this role were invaluable and would transfer well to any future leadership or team-based environment.

PREVIOUS PROJECTS

Integrating VR environment with a Stewart Platform

On-going Honours Project

This project involves the development of a Lunar Rover Simulation utilizing a Stewart Platform, Racing Simulator and VR Headset. Throughout the project, programming of a Unity Engine script to extract kinematic data, integration between all devices and manufacturing of safety equipment were completed.

Computational Fluid Dynamics on a Submarine

March 2022 – June 2022

This project studies the drag coefficient on different nose designs on the hull of Collin's class submarine using Computational Fluid Dynamics.

Finite Element Analysis on a Bird Strike

March 2021 - June 2021

This project investigates Finite Element Methods (FEA) in the analysis of bird strike impacts upon the Cessna 172 wing air foil.

Designing an autonomous weather station

July 2020 – November 2020

This project focuses on the design of an autonomous weather station in terms of a client's needs. Surviving the harsh environments of the arctic and providing accurate data on the wind speed/direction, temperature, snow depth and precipitation.

EDUCATION

The University of Adelaide

Graduating in December 2022

Bachelor of Engineering (Honours) (Mechatronics) | GPA 4.71

Blackfriars Priory School

South Australian Certificate of Education | ATAR 89.96

- All Years High / Highest Honours for yearly academic reports
- Strong presence in the sporting community through being member of the aquatic and badminton teams.

Skills

- Proficient in MATLAB/Simulink, C/C++, Latex, Solidworks/Inventor CAD, Ansys FEA, Ansys CFD, circuit design, Festos, Microsoft Word, Mac OSX, Windows.
- Familiar with HTML, CSS, Java, Python, Solidity.
- Bilingual; English and Vietnamese